{
    "subject": "resource/Joan_Bennett",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthName",
    "object": "Joan Geraldine Bennett",
    "human_readable": "The birth name of Joan Bennett is Joan Geraldine Bennett.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9795408844947815,
            "question": "If Joan Bennett was born as Joan Geraldine Bennett, what is her middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9614256620407104,
            "question": "What is the full birth name of Joan Bennett?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9586898684501648,
            "question": "What was Joan Bennett called at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9559493064880371,
            "question": "What was Joan Bennett's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9278088212013245,
            "question": "Is 'Joan Geraldine Bennett' Joan Bennett's real name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105262160301208,
            "question": "What is the first name of Joan Bennett at birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999491930007935,
            "question": "What are the two given names in Joan Bennett's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8556696772575378,
            "question": "What is the last part of Joan Bennett's birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8378782272338867,
            "question": "Which two words make up Joan Bennett's full birth name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8353306651115417,
            "question": "How many parts are there to Joan Bennett's birth name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth name of Joan Bennett is Joan Geraldine Bennett.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4675_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which two words make up Joan Bennett's full birth name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4675_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the last part of Joan Bennett's birth name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4675_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the two given names in Joan Bennett's birth name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4675_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4675_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThis answer aligns with the information provided in the documents, which state that Joan Bennett's birth name is indeed Joan Geraldine Bennett."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}